[{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8892e"},"rt":19886,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":582667,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8892f"},"rt":10184,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":592965,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88930"},"rt":72746,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":665821,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88931"},"rt":11963,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":678143,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88932"},"rt":26687,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":704958,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88934"},"rt":180923,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":890847,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88935"},"rt":23385,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":914595,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88936"},"rt":85152,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":999861,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88937"},"rt":15388,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1015605,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88938"},"rt":62387,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1078105,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88939"},"rt":9092,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1087535,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8893a"},"rt":8300,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1095938,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8893b"},"rt":35012,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1131054,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8893c"},"rt":40314,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1171492,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8893d"},"rt":45134,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1216736,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8894f"},"rt":34997,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118232,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88950"},"rt":11121,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":129468,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88951"},"rt":22438,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152024,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88952"},"rt":40019,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192158,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z O O O O I I J H H U U C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88953"},"rt":36616,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":228890,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88955"},"rt":11135,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":245028,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88956"},"rt":21140,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266281,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88957"},"rt":51423,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317871,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C B B B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88958"},"rt":39216,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":357200,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I I B B I B F E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88959"},"rt":32683,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390041,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8895a"},"rt":8577,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398735,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8895b"},"rt":7186,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406034,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8895c"},"rt":21395,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":427598,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8895d"},"rt":36625,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464350,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"11 AM11 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8895e"},"rt":57008,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521469,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88970"},"rt":17044,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102308,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88971"},"rt":10880,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113219,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88972"},"rt":13387,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126636,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"7H C A C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88973"},"rt":40834,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167499,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"A 04 PMU U F F O O I J Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88974"},"rt":50286,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217821,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,J","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88976"},"rt":6953,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":227892,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"F 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88977"},"rt":17403,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245331,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88978"},"rt":38327,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283692,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G F B B B I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88979"},"rt":12657,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":296387,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8897a"},"rt":49880,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346307,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8897b"},"rt":12104,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":358444,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8897c"},"rt":6656,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365139,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8897d"},"rt":54097,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":419267,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z Z F F M M M G F F C C O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8897e"},"rt":27247,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":446604,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"N O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8897f"},"rt":20049,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466683,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E X C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88991"},"rt":33320,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147285,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"11 AMC 11 AMZ C 11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88992"},"rt":15718,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163067,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"D D A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88993"},"rt":15353,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":178484,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C C C Z U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88994"},"rt":47667,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":226213,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"Z 03 PM03 PM04 PMB 04 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88995"},"rt":118728,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344998,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88997"},"rt":16929,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":367020,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88998"},"rt":21666,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388741,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"6F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88999"},"rt":44216,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":433022,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8899a"},"rt":26400,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":459478,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"X H J J B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8899b"},"rt":76476,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":536022,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":"F 02 PMF F O F F F F F F F F F F 05 PM06 PMN "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8899c"},"rt":14685,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550894,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3312 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8899d"},"rt":9019,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":559972,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J 03 PM02 PMF F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8899e"},"rt":70979,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":631008,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z 06 PMZ Z N N Z N 06 PMZ Z F Z B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c8899f"},"rt":41854,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":673050,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM03 PM07 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889a0"},"rt":15165,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":688276,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889b2"},"rt":11386,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":559837,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889b3"},"rt":9967,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":573160,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889b4"},"rt":29865,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":603257,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889b5"},"rt":16719,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":622364,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889b6"},"rt":38505,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661696,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889b8"},"rt":8530,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":678458,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889b9"},"rt":17917,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":697278,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889ba"},"rt":37535,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":737005,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889bb"},"rt":26882,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":777294,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":"3B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889bc"},"rt":32534,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":813745,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B F F 04 PMF C B 02 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889bd"},"rt":15026,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":829469,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889be"},"rt":6768,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":837095,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889bf"},"rt":29477,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":871411,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889c0"},"rt":25727,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":900624,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"03 PM03 PM03 PMX M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889c1"},"rt":59073,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":961154,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,J","hovered":"X B F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889d3"},"rt":10523,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79775,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889d4"},"rt":10325,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":90207,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"G H O O O O A A K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889d5"},"rt":10238,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":100554,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C C C C C 09 AMC C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889d6"},"rt":96177,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":196832,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM04 PMB 04 PM03 PMF F Z Z Z Z U K O O H H I I I I 09 AM01 PM02 PMJ O C 09 AM05 PME E K K K K F H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889d7"},"rt":56719,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253921,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"H I 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889d9"},"rt":8099,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":269794,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AME E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889da"},"rt":24267,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294169,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I E B M O X 12 PM01 PMO X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889db"},"rt":71505,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365906,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"9B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889dc"},"rt":48137,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":414413,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J 09 AMJ J I B B 3I E E G 02 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889dd"},"rt":34985,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":449770,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z Z X X A F 10 AMB F M Z 02 PM02 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889de"},"rt":10297,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":460172,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889df"},"rt":8764,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469043,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"E B F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889e0"},"rt":42640,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":511793,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"G G G X N Z 02 PMB O Z Z F Z Z Z H C C G E E E E F F E E F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889e1"},"rt":26344,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":538247,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM03 PMO H C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889e2"},"rt":51503,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":590117,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM02 PMZ Z H G H C H H Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889f4"},"rt":9274,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1412984,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889f5"},"rt":8184,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1421270,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"D 8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889f6"},"rt":47481,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1468858,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"1010C 10 AMC 04 PM05 PM06 PM05 PMB 05 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889f7"},"rt":29085,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1498051,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AM03 PM703 PMC A 06 PM4I X X 08 AM05 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889f8"},"rt":68045,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1566203,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I I I 12 PMI I 11 AMI I I O I 11 AM11 AMZ O 8O 5512 PMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889fa"},"rt":35916,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1615317,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"H H G E A E G 06 PM11 AM03 PM04 PM05 PM03 PM02 PMM B B F F F F J 10 AMJ 09 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889fb"},"rt":36979,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1652407,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"89B O D N N D 2D X M F F B B B F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889fc"},"rt":35215,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1687708,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"B B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889fd"},"rt":43852,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1731662,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O O J I B I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889fe"},"rt":6909,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1738680,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"4F F B B M 01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c889ff"},"rt":6629,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1745411,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J J M 02 PM01 PM12 PMF F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a00"},"rt":12345,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1757859,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B 12 PM12 PMF F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a01"},"rt":42468,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1800428,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"Z H H H Z Z N N 06 PM06 PMZ Z Z Z H Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a02"},"rt":17822,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1818361,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM04 PM03 PMX X 03 PMX B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a03"},"rt":69041,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1887514,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"06 PM02 PMF E 01 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMB 03 PM11 AM10 AMF F B 04 PM07 PM04 PM03 PMZ 02 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMM M M M 5M L L M 8G C 02 PM01 PM12 PMM M M B X X B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a15"},"rt":39029,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141630,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O O 08 AM11 AM10 AM11 AMA A A A 12 PM11 AM11 AMF 211 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a16"},"rt":11601,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153264,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"12 PM12 PM01 PMD K 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a17"},"rt":31405,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184700,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"310 AM09 AMC F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a18"},"rt":48586,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233316,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"Z 04 PMH H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a19"},"rt":133705,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367053,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"709 AMC I 01 PM01 PMU I I 11 AMU U 08 AM08 AM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMI A O C O O O O O O O O I I I O O C O I I O O A F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a1b"},"rt":40977,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":421841,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E 6G G C C C C 04 PM03 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a1c"},"rt":22615,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":444490,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F Z Z Z F Z O F O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a1d"},"rt":109601,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":554119,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"7F F B G B B B B B F F B G E C C C C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a1e"},"rt":81664,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":635870,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I E J J I E J I J J J J I J I 6J B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a1f"},"rt":13803,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":649751,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B F F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a20"},"rt":12129,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661912,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"112 PMM L M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a21"},"rt":85942,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":747881,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a22"},"rt":16095,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":764055,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a23"},"rt":7937,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":772024,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a24"},"rt":55716,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":827774,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"E 12 PM01 PM02 PMX 2K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a36"},"rt":26590,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212329,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMA A 12 PM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a37"},"rt":23749,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":236257,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U F E E G E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a38"},"rt":20466,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256854,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A C C C 10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a39"},"rt":31057,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288049,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM04 PMG 04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a3a"},"rt":21607,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":309818,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a3c"},"rt":104337,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":422209,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMJ J 10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMG 08 PM04 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a3d"},"rt":23413,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445820,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a3e"},"rt":55861,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":501810,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G G 2C B E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a3f"},"rt":19451,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":521408,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I 3I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a40"},"rt":87274,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":608791,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,X","hovered":"4F F F Z F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a41"},"rt":15113,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":624060,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM11 AM02 PM01 PM12 PMB F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a42"},"rt":7199,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":631432,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a43"},"rt":42312,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":673865,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B X Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a44"},"rt":46309,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":720306,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O 03 PMO G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a45"},"rt":47791,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":768197,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PMX X 01 PMC 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a57"},"rt":13985,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205404,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C 11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a58"},"rt":140089,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345554,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"09 AM08 AMD D D D 12 PM11 AMA D D D E E 04 PM04 PMB B 04 PM03 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM11 AM11 AMD D E D D K U 12 PM12 PMD D D 88J D D D D D E H 6H E E E D D D D 8D D D D D D E E E E E U U 01 PMU E E H E E E U D D D D D E K D D D K Z D J D D D D K K K K D D D D K 12 PMK D K K 12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM11"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a59"},"rt":70772,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416543,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"H Z C C C C C 2C C C C C A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a5a"},"rt":264962,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":681703,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PMG B 04 PM04 PM4C A U U U U U A A F F F F K K K Z Z F F O O O O J J J I O O O O O O X X J I I B B 04 PM03 PMU F F K K Z Z A A A C O O H H F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a5b"},"rt":210680,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":892570,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.75,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,O,J,H","hovered":"77I I I I I I J J J C O J J C J O O O 03 PM03 PMA C O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a5d"},"rt":24513,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":923613,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM08 AM308 AM08 AM13E G G G E E E G G E G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a5e"},"rt":41562,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":965238,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J I I B B I F B O O X X O O X X X 09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a5f"},"rt":297972,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1263273,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B J J J B J J J J I I I J J I I I B B B E E E E G E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a60"},"rt":38582,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1302054,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I I E I I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a61"},"rt":185433,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1487549,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I F F F F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a62"},"rt":18914,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1506667,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"09 AM11 AM12 PM09 AM10 AM11 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a63"},"rt":12405,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1519133,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a64"},"rt":87236,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1606429,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E Z N D Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a65"},"rt":183793,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1790425,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"402 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d838b40a7aae4618c88a66"},"rt":107308,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1897951,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"C C J J F M M Z 3"}]
